He runs after me, grabs me, and he goes,
"What the are you doing?" And I go,
"Living, bro." And I punch him in the
face and run away. Like, there's happy
drunk, there's sad drunk, I was runaway
drunk.
Very, very funny man. He's got his own
podcast called My Dumb Friends. Give it
up for Dan Mintz.
Drugs and alcohol have affected every
area of my life. It's affected my
relationship with women and my
relationship with sex. This is small
aside, I spent $1,500 to have a escort
come over one night and I couldn't get
it up, so I just spent all night holding
her hand
like it was the first date.
Bro, I'm like, "Hey, if I pay extra, can
we do that animal cracker scene from
Armageddon?"
I It's affected It's affected my
relationship with my family. My family
once once I was naked in my parents'
living room doing lines. Naked's the
official uniform of cocaine, by the way.
That's like Superman's cape. And they
came home early and the only thing that
I could think to SAY WAS, "HUH? HUH?
DON'T COME IN, I'M MASTURBATING."
You know your wife's in a sad place if
masturbation's the safe option with your
parents.
And then when they turned their back, I
took the rest of the cocaine, put it in
a bag, and shoved it up my ass so I
could do the cocaine in the basement
while they were asleep before they got
up for work at 6:00 a.m. I did coke the
same way Gollum eats.
Uh
It's the the biggest area of my life
it's affected are uh are my my
relationships with my friends, my my my
friendships. When I was 20 years old, I
was actually a janitor at a middle
school, which at the time didn't fit.
Now now it looks like it fits. Like now
Now I look like the guy who's like,
"Hey, if you kids want to miss
dodgeball, I'll tell you how I got this
hook, you know?" Uh
But uh
at the time it didn't fit. I was very
clean
face. And my friend called me up and he
said, "Hey, I got tickets to the
Gathering of the Vibes. It's this jam
band festival in upstate New York."
Yeah, it's all it was like I had like I
had a really I went there in high
school. I had a really fun time there in
high school. Did a lot of drugs. I met a
chick. It was it was great,
right? And I'm 20 At this point like I'm
getting way more It's like my up
times are getting way more dark. But I'm
excited because I'm like working a
shitty job. My wife's in a shitty place.
I'm like, "All right, I have something
to look forward to on on one of these
janitor weekends." Uh
That sounds like the worst buddy comedy
ever. Get ready for Janitor Weekends
starring Zach Braff and another Zach.
Still a Zach in that movie. Anyway,
my friend picks me up. We stop at the My
friend John He picks me up. We stop at
the liquor store. He already should have
known there was going to be a problem
that weekend cuz he got a 12-pack of
beer and I bought like a handle of Black
Velvet Whiskey.
He's like, "Oh my god, there's like
that's like that's like what you drink
in in like a baby shower on Deadwood,
you know? So
We get we get in the car. I'm I'm
getting like hammered the whole
trip to this and I'm I'm I'm just
getting I'm just getting drunker. I'm
not making I'm like starting to argue
with him like it's not making any sense
and we get to Gathering of the Vibes and
at this like Gathering of the Vibes has
changed since the like last time I was
there it was like peace, love, and
understanding. Now there's like one good
vibe and all the other vibes are I
wonder how much ecstasy I can get if I
steal that guy's iPod, you know? Uh
And we like we're in the car, we're
arguing, and then all of a sudden like
we're on one we're like in in a car line
waiting to go into this festival and the
back door opens and I swear to god this
old man walks in and he looked like
imagine if like Burt's Bees had like a
cousin but instead of selling bee
he just sold the milk he squeezed from
possums, you know? Uh
And he's he sits down
and we look at him and he just goes,
"Don't mind me, passing through." And he
passes out in the back
like it was
like it was a bonus round on Oregon
Trail.
But I'm such a drunk my friend doesn't
even notice that because I'm already
like I'm already yelling at him
and I'm like I'm like he's like, "Stop
with the air conditioner." And
I'm like, "Your mom's an air
conditioner." He's like, "That doesn't
make any sense. Stop playing Stevie
Nicks Landslide." I'm like, "It's a good
song. Go yourself."
Uh
We're fighting back and forth. We're
fighting so much that in the middle of
it the old guy just wakes up and he
goes, "Okay." And he leaves.
Like I was so annoying I made a hobo
turn down shelter. That's how annoying I
was. He's like, "I rather die in the
cold than deal with this I'm going
back to hobo island." Uh
But we're fighting more and more uh
you know we're coming down to the 10
area. He's like you down. I'm like
you. He's like what's your problem?
The Iraq war was wrong. He's like you're
not making any sense. I jump out of the
car as it's driving. Now this sounds
like very lethal weaponry and impressive
but the car was only going 10 miles an
hour. So it just looked like the most
low stakes hostage situation ever.
So he stops the car. He runs after me.
He grabs me and he goes what the
are you doing? And I go living bro and I
punch him in the face and run away. Like
there's happy drunk, there's sad drunk.
I was runaway drunk.
I don't remember much of the night.
What I do remember is I remember I had
taken two hits of acid and I was nervous
because I drank so much that I was going
to pass out and not experience the acid.
So I bought a gram of cocaine.
That I I immediately did to my dome and
I remember I turned to the guy who sold
me the cocaine and I'm like you want to
talk now? And he goes I'm cool and he
walks away. So he's probably a doctor
now. Uh
And then that's all I remember. I pass
out and then I woke up the next day and
I was in my friend's trunk and the trunk
was open and my friend is like sitting
in the corner like he's like sitting on
one of those like camp chairs and he's
smoking a cigarette and he's looking off
into the distance and it's just that
palpable feeling of I up you know
and I turn to him and I'm like
Hey John.
He goes what?
I go I'm sorry.
He goes sorry for what?
For punching you in the face?
And then he goes the first time or the
second time? Apparently later in the
night I punched him in the face again.
That wasn't a good scene. I I walked
away. I found like like this like little
creek near the tent. Not creek, it was
like just kind of a ditch and I started
like puking cuz I was hungover
from that. It looked like the whole
thing was like the most white trash
Ansel Adams photo ever.
And then this dude comes up in back of
me and then I just hear "Rico?"
And I'm like what No, no. And I start
I'm like forcing myself to puke and he's
like Ri- Rico? He's like I'm like I'm
not Rico. I'm not Rico. And then he
goes, "No, you're Rico." I'm like I'm
not Rico. And then he takes out
his digital camera
and he shows the pictures and I had been
partying with that guy
the night before and told him my name
was Rico.
And I got like I'm so sorry. He goes,
"No, don't worry, man. You were
hilarious. You told great stories. You
helped my friend Mike through a
breakup."
You like played him this Bob Dylan song
that helped.
And then he he goes, "How's law school
going?" I told him I was going to law
school.
Yeah, he goes, "Good. It's good."
And then he goes, "Dude, you dude come
here, come here." And then he like puts
a clump of mushrooms in my hand.
And I look at it and I'm like, "Well,
when in Upstate New York and I eat the
mushrooms." Cut to like a half hour
later. At this point I'm like starting
to feel the body buzz and he goes, "Hey,
dance for us like you did last night."
And I'm like, "What?" So, I start
dancing and they think it's hilarious,
but I think it's sexy cuz I'm tripping.
Like it looked like if Jabba danced for
Leia, you know? It was like the opposite
of what it normally is. So, and then I
start dancing away from them, but then
they followed me and we're all dancing
in this line through the festival and in
the distance I see my friend John and he
looks at his he goes, "What the
DAN?"
AND THEN
THE GUY IN BACK OF ME GOES, "IT'S NOT
DAN, IT'S RICO."
AND THEN HE GOES, "IT'S DAN."
AND HE'S LIKE, "NO, IT'S RICO." AND then
John like, "It's Dan." And then the guy
uh
reaches in his pocket, pulls out some
more mushrooms, goes up to my friend
John, uh puts it in his hand
and my
friend John looks at the mushrooms, he
goes, "You know,
you know, Dan was rude, obnoxious,
violent, and drunk last night, but uh
this guy Rico, well,
he seems pretty cool." And he ate the
mushrooms and then we all partied
together.
It was uh two rehabs later, I'm still
dancing. Guys, thank you so much. Have a
good night.